可以给我看漫画吗？
Can I see the comics?
这是纽约时报
This is the New York Times.
好，能否借我看漫画？
Okay,may I see the comics?
你们不是要带罗斯去看球？
I thought you were taking Ross to the game.
是啊，我们约在这里 瑞秋也跟我们约在这里
-We are. He's meeting us here. -No,Rachel's meeting us here!
他们还是可以共处一室吧
Come on! They can be in the same room.
你昨晚没看到 怎么了？
-You should've been there last night. -What happened?
罗斯在我们那边
Ross was hanging out at our place.
瑞秋来跟钱德借润肤乳…
Rachel comes over to borrow some moisturizer from Chandler
你不能说借“东西”吗？
How hard is it to say "something"?
瑞秋过来借“东西”
Rachel came over to borrow "something."
反正她和罗斯就开始对骂
Anyway,her and Ross just started yelling at each other.
他怎么敢骂她？ 他跟别人上床耶
Why was he yelling at her? He slept with someone else.
他说他们当时分手了
He says they were on a break when it happened...
所以她早就该原谅他了
...so she should've forgiven him by now.
他真不可理喻，真是的
He is so unreasonable! God!
不过我了解他的意思
Although I understand what he means.
天哪，这样好像“60分钟”
Oh,my God! This is like 60 Minutes...
你本来很气制药公司 生产一种药
...when at first you're mad that pharmaceutical company made the drug.
后来又很同情那些人，因为…
And then,you just feel bad for the people,because...
他们想要长头发
...they needed to make their hair grow.
我父母离婚时就是这样
You know,this is like when my parents got divorced.
希望罗斯看完球 不会企图绑架我
I hope Ross doesn't try to kidnap me after Cub Scouts.
我梦到罗斯和瑞秋没有分手
I dreamed that Ross and Rachel were still together.
我们开心的在一起
And we were all hanging out and happy.
我也梦到了
I had the same dream.
-没有人跟那个女的上床 -我的刚好相反
-And nobody slept with the xerox girl. -Oh,I had the opposite dream.
也许不要紧，都一个星期了
Maybe it's gonna be okay. I mean,it's been a week.
我结束一段感情 从不超过一星期
It never takes me more than a week to get over a relationship.
你一冲完澡 一段感情就结束了
It never takes you more than a shower to get over a relationship.
走吧，上路了，我们去玩吧
Let's go! Let's hit the road. Let's get the show on it.
我先喝杯咖啡
Let me get coffee.
附近有一家很棒的咖啡馆
I know the best coffeehouse. And it's close.
比这里近？
Closer than here?
你看，我找到一杯
Oh,look! I found coffee!
我们走吧
Okay,let's skedaddle.
我才不喝别人喝剩的
I'm not gonna drink somebody's old coffee.
是，殿下
Okay,Your Highness.
“瑞秋，对不起” “没关系，你想复合吗？”
"Rachel,I'm really sorry." "Okay,Ross. Wanna get back together?"
“好啊”
"Yeah,okay."
你们有听到吗？
Did anyone else hear that?
本集播出：“滑雪出行”
The One Without the Ski Trip
他在吗？
Is he here?
你的润肤乳
Here's your moisturizer.
你们会爱死我！听我说
You guys are gonna love me! Okay,check it out.
周四晚上，五张票
Thursday night,five tickets.
卡文克莱内衣秀 你们要跟我一起去
Calvin Klein lingerie show,and you guys are coming with me.
我有说出声音来吧？
I said that out loud,right?
有，只是我们已经…
Yes,it's just that we kind of already...
跟罗斯有约了
... made plans with Ross.
好吧
Well,okay.
就这样吧
Well,there you go.
他买了新的家庭影院组合
It's just,he got this new home-theater dealy...
想找我们去看
...and he wants us to check it out.
他很兴奋
He's excited about it too.
还在答录机里录了节目表
He even recorded showtimes on his answering machine.
对不起 没关系
-We're sorry,honey. -Oh,it's okay.
不是我们不想去，真的
Rach,it's not that we don't want to. Really.
模特儿穿内衣走秀？
Are we talking models in their underwear?
还有高跟鞋
And heels.
罗斯先开口，我们也排好了
Ross did ask us first,and we set that night aside.
没关系，是他先约的，很公平
Come on. If he asked you first,it's only fair.
我好受不了
Oh,boy,do I feel bad!
非常受不了
Very bad.
钱德，你在干什么？
Chandler,what are you doing?
天哪
Oh,my God!
你又抽烟了？
You're smoking again?
那是昨天
Well,actually,yesterday,I was smoking again.
今天是“还在抽”
Today I'm smoking,still.
嚼了那么多戒烟口香糖 为什么又开始抽了？
Why would you start again after chewing all that quitting gum?
我父母离婚时就像这样
This is just like my parents' divorce...
害我学会抽烟
...which is when I first started smoking.
你当时不是才9岁？
Weren't you 9?
午睡后来一根最过瘾
I'm telling you something,that first smoke after naptime....
好啊，我猜是他
That's great. With my luck,that's him.
罗斯？
Him? Ross?
不，是赞美诗253篇 “他看顾麻雀”（圣歌）
No,"Hymn" 253: "His Eyes Are on the Sparrow."
我父母离婚后 我开始用幽默来自卫
When my parents got divorced,I started using humor as a defense mechanism.
你们周末有计划吗？
Hi. Do you guys have weekend plans?
我妹说周末 可以到她的小屋去滑雪
Because my sister says we can spend the weekend at her cabin,skiing.
是我先问的吧？ 我有遵守游戏规则
I'm asking you first,right? I'm playing by the rules.
没问题
Absolutely.
钱德，你抽烟？你怎么搞的？
Chandler! You're smoking? What are you doing?
闭嘴，你又不是我的亲娘
Shut up! You're not my real mom!
关窗子好吗？ 我的乳头硬到可以割玻璃
Could you close that window? My nipples could cut glass!
真的？我的让我躲掉罚单
Really? Because mine get me out of tickets.
真的很谢谢你们来陪我
Look,I just wanna say I really appreciate you spending time with me.
这阵子很难熬，真的谢谢你们
It's been a hard time right now,so I just want to say thanks.
谁去抱抱他 我得留在窗子旁边
Somebody else hug him. I have to stay by the window.
周末要不要来个影碟马拉松？
How about this weekend,we have a laser-disc marathon,okay?
或是来比赛，我有新的…
And maybe a tournament on my new...
飞镖盘！怎么样？
...dart board! What do you think?
连射两天飞镖，一定很好玩
Two days of darts! It'll be great!
不如排在下周末
It'll be great for next weekend.
不，这个周末
This weekend,guys.
不如排在下周末
It'll be great for next weekend.
一定会很好玩
I mean,"lt'll be great."
怎么回事？
What's going on?
我们被找去滑雪 要去瑞秋的妹妹的小屋
We're sort of invited to go skiing. You know,Rachel's sister's cabin?
整个周末？
So,for the whole weekend?
对不起，是她先约的
We're really sorry,but she did ask us first.
没关系，我失恋的第一个周末
That's okay. If you all have to go away...
你们都要出城去
...for the first weekend I'm alone by myself...
我完全可以理解
...then I totally understand.
我可以留下来，我留下来
I can stay. I'm gonna stay.
上次去滑雪 我根本不敢下缆车
The last time I went,I was afraid to leave the chair lift.
就这样坐来坐去
I just went round and round.
你得开你外婆的车载我们去
We need you to drive us there in your grandmother's cab.
这样吧，我留下来 不，我留，他是我的哥哥
-But you know what? I'll stay. -No,I'll stay. He's my brother.
这是同情吗？
What,a "pity stay"?
我们会玩得很开心
We're gonna have fun!
我们来做牛奶软糖
We can make fudge.
同情的食物？
Pity food?
没关系，我不需要你们留下来
You know what? I don't need any of you to stay.
谁都不准留下来
Nobody stays.
那我也表示一下“留下”的意思好了
Well,then,I might as well offer to stay.
有人在替罗斯难过吗？
Does anybody else feel bad about Ross?
你觉得他还在生气？
You think he's still mad?
更气了，你居然跟他借护目镜
He's probably more mad since you called him to borrow his goggles.
怎样？我的没有颜色
What? Mine aren't tinted.
钱德？   怎样？
Chandler   What?
标示说什么？
What does the sign say?
“主耶稣，请照耀我”
"Beam me up,Jesus."
是“禁止吸烟”的标示
The "No Smoking" sign.
我外婆的车上不能抽烟
There's no smoking in my grandmother's cab.
那我要上厕所
Well,then,I have to go to the bathroom.
拜托
Oh,please!
没事不准停车 加油的时候再去
No unscheduled stops. You can go when we stop for gas.
那边有休息站 我真的得上厕所
There's a rest stop right up there. Come on,I really have to go!
现在我也想上了
Oh,now I have to go!
这事儿还会传染吗？  有时只是一阵微风就可以…
ls that all that it takes?Sometimes just a small breeze....
到了
Here we go.
坐好 什么？
-Brace yourself! -What?
你不去？ 不了
-Aren't you gonna go? -No,thanks.
瑞秋不上公共厕所
Rachel never pees in public restrooms.
里面都没有马桶垫纸
They never have any paper in there.
所以我决定 没有纸就不嘘嘘
So my rule is,"No tissue,no tushy."
既然大家都下车了…
Well,if everybody's going....
别关门！钥匙在里面
Don't close it! The keys are in there!
怎么了？ 打火机在里面
-What's going on? -My lighter's in there!
妈的 排气管不够烫，点不着
Damn! The tailpipe's not hot enough to light this.
我会开门，谁有衣架？
I can open this. Anybody got a coat hanger?
我有
Oh,I do.
不对，早上穿衣服时拿掉了
No,I took it out of my shirt when I put it on this morning.
要是你的父母没有离婚
So if your parents hadn't divorced...
你就能正常的回答问题？
...you'd be able to answer a question like a normal person?
我需要铁丝类的东西把它撬开
Look,I just need a wire something to jimmy it.
把你们内衣的钢丝给我
One of you give me your bra underwire.
快，谁的胸部最大？
Come on! Who has the biggest boobs?
胸部最大，内衣的钢丝也最长
Whoever has the biggest boobs,has the biggest bra and wire.
不要 很贵耶
-No! -It's too expensive!
有钢丝才能回车上
To get back in the car,we need that wire.
你们决定
Your call.
莫妮卡最大
Monica's are the biggest.
这两粒小的平胸？拜托！ 绝对是瑞秋
These tiny little non-breasts? Please! It's gotta be Rachel.
不对，我的是骗人的
No,mine are deceptively small.
我有时候还会垫东西
I mean,I actually sometimes stuff my bra.
所以你的内衣还是很大
Well,then,your bra would still be big.
我都垫在内衣外面
No,I stuff outside the bra.
小姐们，你们就让步吧
Ladies,let's just compromise,okay?
菲比、瑞秋 脱了莫妮卡的胸罩
Phoebe,Rachel,take off Monica's bra.
好啦，算了
All right,forget it,never mind.
我脱 谢谢
-You can have mine. -Thank you.
你干什么？那里就有垃圾桶
What are you doing? There's a trash can right there.
我以为只要我乱扔垃圾 那个哭泣的印第安人就会来救咱们（一则关于环保的公益广告））
I thought if I littered,that crying lndian might come by and save us.
拿去
There.
菲比，谢了，你真大方
Thank you,Phoebe. That's very,very generous.
哇哦，真不错，你打算这样去约会？
Wow. This is nice. Were you planning on meeting somebody up there?
现在来比谁的屁股翘
Now,let's decide who has the nicest ass.
上车吧
And there you go!
至少让我爽一下
Well,at least let me smoke it to the good part!
怎么搞的？ 怎么了？
-What's going on? -What?
我碰过这种状况
Yeah,this has happened before.
那你会修？ 会，加点天然气就行了
-So you know how to fix it? -Yep. Put more gas in.
你怎么来了？
Hi. What are you doing here?
我在想，我们分手时
I was wondering,when you and I split up...
你有没有分到一卷带子 录了《风流医生俏护士》的最后一集
...did you get the tape that was half the last episode of M.A. S.H...
和人质回国的新闻？
...and half the hostages coming home?
现在是苏珊和我游墨西哥 和人质回国的新闻
But now it's Susan and me in Mexico and the hostages coming home.
班呢？
Where's Ben?
在睡觉
He's sleeping.
我来得不是时候？
Is this a bad time?
没错，苏珊马上就要来了
Yeah,actually. Susan's gonna be here any minute.
今天是个纪念日
It's kind of an anniversary.
你们不是一月结婚的吗？
I thought you guys got married in January.
是另一个纪念日
A different kind of anniversary.
总之…
So anyway
蜡烛、香槟
Candles,champagne....
纪念日真好
Yeah,anniversaries are great...
因为爱是永恒的
... because love lasts forever,you know?
什么也比不上爱情可靠，放在银行里的钱
There's nothing like it in this life. Money in the bank.
瑞秋和我分手了
So Rachel and I broke up.
天哪，真遗憾
God,Ross,I am so sorry!
你知道吗？
You know what?
我很想陪你聊一聊
I wanna talk about this so much...
但要找个能长谈的时间
... but when we can really get into it.
明天晚餐可以吗？ 太好了
-You free for dinner tomorrow? -I'd love that.
我也是
Me too.
一切都是因为瑞秋找到新工作
I guess it all started when Rachel got this new job.
3A（美国汽车联合会）可以来拖车
Triple A can pick us up.
我们靠近哪个镇？
What town are we near?
佛利蒙
Fremont.
威斯蒙特
Westmont.
威斯柏格？
Westberg?
为什么你非要回答
Why are you answering?
我们在哪条路上？
Do you know what route we're on?
绝对是27号公路
We are definitely on Route 27.
我们在27号公路一个休息站
We are at a rest stop on Route 27
没有27号公路
There is no Route 27.
不是93号就是76号 我不知道
-Either 93 or 76. -I don't know.
我每次来都在后座睡觉
I always slept in the back when we drove here.
能不能请人 沿着76号公路找？
Can you just send someone up and down 76 and check every rest stop?
还有93号公路？
And also 93?
他们不干
No,they don't do that.
一定会有人来救我们
Somebody will come and save us.
谁？这一个半小时 有车子经过吗？
Who? Have you seen a car in the last hour and a half?
应该找罗斯 他可以借车来载我们
We should call Ross. Maybe he can get a car to get us.
我不要跟罗斯同车
I am not getting in a car with Ross!
我们必须…
We will just have to...
耗在这里
...Iive here!
但是好冷 不行
-But it's so cold. -No!
我不跟他同车，想别的办法
I won't get in a car with him. Think of something else.
乔伊和钱德回来了
Joey and Chandler are back!
求援过程很顺利？
So the "going for help" went well?
老烟枪走到一半就挂了
Smokey Joe here got halfway to the highway and collapsed.
我的肺活量跟两岁小孩一样
I have the lung capacity of a 2-year-old.
那你为什么还要抽烟？
Then why are you smoking?
我很不安
It's very unsettling.
对吧？真是太不可思议了
Right? I mean,it's pretty unbelievable.
他们就这样头也不回的出发
They just took off,without even looking back.
我不需要他们 我有你们这些朋友
I don't need them. I've got you guys now as friends.
你和苏珊
You and Susan.
苏珊会很高兴
Susan will be so pleased.
717？
Seven-one-seven?
717是哪里？
Where's 717?
你有帮苏珊留吧？
You have more of these for Susan,right?
没有，不过没关系
No,but that's okay.
还有腌黄瓜什么的可以吃
I'll just put out pickles or something.
罗斯，谢天谢地 菲比？
-Ross,thank God! -Pheebs?
为什么这么小声？
Why are you whispering?
我吃了一只虫子
I ate a bug.
瑞秋，这里的棉条只要一美分
Hey,Rach! The tampons here are only a penny.
我们买来屯积
Let's stock up.
我们没油了，又不知道方位 没办法叫拖车
We're out of gas and don't know where we are so we can't get a tow truck.
现在需要帮忙了？
Now you want a favor?
对，拜托
Yes,please.
很抱歉你们的车子挂了
I'm sorry your car broke down,Pheebs...
但是我忙着跟真朋友联络感情
... but I'm too busy with some of my real friends right now.
等你们安全到家，记得通知我
But please call to let me know you got home safely.
菲比，等一下
Phoebe,hang on a second.
开我的车去接你朋友
Take my car. Get your friends.
我才不要去接他们
No,I won't pick them up.
我们都知道你会去 因为你不是混蛋
We both know you'll do it,because you're not a jerk.
你顶多再骂个半小时 还是会去接他们
So you can sulk here for half an hour,then go get them...
不如节省时间去车上骂 瑞秋不会…
-...or save time and sulk in the car. -Rachel doesn't
很遗憾瑞秋为了马克甩了你
I'm sorry Rachel dumped you for Mark...
你是无辜的受害者
...and you're the innocent victim in this.
但不要为了瑞秋牵怒你的朋友
But don't punish your friends for what Rachel did.
你说得对
Yeah,you're right.
菲比，等一下，罗斯要跟你说
Phoebe,hang on. Ross wants to say something.
什么？
What?
你跟别人上床？
You slept with someone else?
我们当时在分手
We were on a break!
我们…
We were
你们在哪里？我去找
Where are you? I'll find you.
你跟别的女人上床？
You slept with another woman?
你还敢说我？
Oh,you're one to talk.
好了
Okay,done!
什么是“命救”？
What's "pleh"?
就是“救命”反过来
That's "help" spelled backwards...
好让直升机上的人看得懂
...so that the helicopters can read it from the air.
“呆子”反过来怎么写？
What's "dufus" spelled backwards?
有车子！
Car! Car!
罗斯出来兜风了
Oh,it's Ross on one of his drives!
他来干什么？
What is he doing here?
他来救你们一命
He is saving your butt.
除非我惹到了某个人
Unless I'm stepping on some toes here...
那我可以闪人
...in which case I could just mosey on.
州际公路上有很多人需要我帮助
I have plenty of people to help on the interstate.
别这样 我们需要你
-Come on! -We need your help,please!
好好好
Fine! Fine!
完了，别人看不出来了
Oh,no! Now it's not gonna make any sense.
喂…
You guys...
罗斯怎么办？他大老远跑来
...what do we do about Ross? He drove all the way up here.
难道要叫他回去 我们自己去滑雪？
Just send him back,then we'll go skiing?
烦死了
This is horrible. It's just horrible.
要找罗斯一起去吗？
Should we ask Ross to come along?
那瑞秋呢？要怎么向她开口？
But what about Rachel? How are we gonna even ask her?
开什么口？
Ask me what?
罗斯能不能去滑雪？
If it might be okay if Ross came skiing?
我才没有要问
No,I wasn't gonna ask that.
你们太扯了 不行，他不能去
You guys are unbelievable. No,he cannot come!
什么？ 烦死了
-Excuse me? -It's horrible!
求求你，让我去你的神奇小屋
Oh,please? Can't I come to your special,magical cabin?
你去干什么？你滑雪滑得很烂
Why would you even want to come? You're a horrible skier.
真是说到我的痛处啊！我的滑雪技术
Hitting me where it hurts! My ski skills!
又来了
Here we go again.
我没办法处理
I can't handle this,you guys.
我有办法 “处理”是我的名字
I can handle it. "Handle" is my middle name.
我的名字（Chandler）去头去尾就是处理（handle）
Actually,it's the middle part of my first name.
菲比，你的车子好了
All right,Pheebs,your cab's ready.
走吧
Let's go.
不客气
You're welcome.
抱歉，你在跟我说话 还是跟别人上床？
I'm sorry. Were you speaking to me,or sleeping with someone else?
我们当时分手了
We were on a break!
你干脆在答录机里留这句话
Why don't you just put that on your answering machine?
本来就是，不只我这么想
It's valid,and I'm not the only one who thinks so.
莫妮卡也同意
Monica agrees with me.
什么？
What?
我不知道
I don't know.
你昨晚说的
You said it last night.
我是说我能理解
What I said was that I understood.
乔伊才认同你
Joey is the one who agreed with you.
是吗，乔伊？
Really,Joey?
什么？
What?
这件事没有对错
You know what? There is no right or wrong here.
我觉得错的是谁很明显
I think it's very obvious who's wrong here.
乔伊不这么想
Obviously not to Joey.
什么？
What?
乔伊和莫妮卡跟我感觉一样 你只会装无辜
-Joey and Monica feel the way I do! -You and this innocent puppy act!
你们猜我在学谁？
Hey,guess who I am?
看看你们把钱德害得多惨！
Look what you're doing to Chandler!
听着，我们知道你们都很难受
Look. We know that this is really,really hard for you guys.
你们不必爱对方
You don't have to love each other.
你们现在甚至不必喜欢对方
You don't even have to like each other much right now.
但是请设法和平相处
But please,find a way to be around each other.
别让我们左右为难
And not put us in the middle.
否则我们以后就不用在一起了
Otherwise,I mean,that's just it for us hanging out together.
你们真的想这样？
Is that what you want?
讲理一点好吗？
Can you be civil?
我可以
I can.
很好，回车上吧，冷死了
Good,let's get back in the car. It's freezing...
我的胸部没有保护
...and my chest is unsupported.
等一下
Wait a second!
现在是怎样？谁要跟谁走？
I mean,what are we doing? Who's going with who?
你们去吧
Look,you guys should go.
你们都计划好了
You know,you planned this all out...
我不想破坏，你们去吧
...and I don't wanna ruin it. So just go.
你大老远开车来
You drove all the way up here.
反正我得去还车
I've got to take the car back anyway.
我明天一整天都要陪班
I'm spending all day tomorrow with Ben.
没关系，你们去吧 不要有罪恶感，真的
It's fine,okay? Just go. No guilt,I promise.
谢谢
Thank you.
回去再打电话给你
We'll call you when we get back.
我们可以去看电影
Maybe we can,like,go to a movie or something.
或是去看马术表演
Or the rodeo!
听起来不错
That would be great.
我刚才在学《海神号遇险记》里的雪莉温特斯
I was being Shelley Winters from The Poseidon Adventure.
我知道
I know.
再见
Bye!
抱歉这么晚
Hi. Sorry I'm late.
你在睡觉？
Were you sleeping?
那就好
Oh,great.
你的车子得换电池 我换了一个最好的
I had to get you a new battery. I got the best I could.
这种钱不能省
You don't want to skimp there.
你真聪明
You're a genius.
花了112元
It came to about $112.
算了，算110就好
But what the hell,call it an even 110?
明天给你，再见
I'll pay you tomorrow. Bye!
他们都走了
So they all took off.
看他们离开蛮难受的
It was pretty hard watching them go,you know?
好，再见
Yeah,okay. Bye.
那我走
So I'm gonna take off then.